恶魔城
第四季 第８集
‎恶心的东西
Nasty stuff.
‎贝尔蒙特
The Belmont.
‎我希望赢得体面
I was hoping for a proper win.
‎你是说打得体面吗
Don't you mean a proper fight?
‎不
No.
‎因为我一定会赢
Because I'm going to win.
‎它在哪里 ‎那个该死的东西在哪儿
Where is it? Where's the fucking thing?
‎我要找一面大镜子 镜框上有字
Looking for a big mirror. There's writing on the frame.
‎一切都会从中消失
Things disappear through it.
不知道吗
No?
‎该死的废物
Bloody useless.
‎如果你不帮我找到那面镜子
Now, how am I supposed to orchestrate the return of Dracula himself
‎我怎么让德古拉伯爵起死回生
if you won't help me find the fucking mirror?
‎我不是在这附近安排了一些弓箭手吗
Didn't I leave some archers around here somewhere?
‎消灭吸血鬼
At the vampires.
‎我想我们引起了他们的注意
I believe we have their attention.
‎我想我们激怒了他们
I think we pissed them off.
‎现在得进去了吧
Time to go indoors?
‎我也是这么想的
Oh, I very much think so.
‎进去 退后
Inside. Fall back.
‎进去
Inside.
‎尽可能多地
It may be a good idea
‎把重物拖到大门后也许是个好主意
to drag as many heavy things over to this door as we can.
‎我需要有人拿着剑
And I want someone with a sword
‎站到窗口的每一个弓箭手旁边
next to every archer at the windows.
‎往后退三步
And keep three steps back.
‎我猜那些混蛋能爬上来
I assume those fuckers can climb.
‎我早该想到的
I should have thought of that.
‎你很走运 现在有我来打理你的生活
Lucky you have me here to run your life for you now.
‎那是什么
What's that?
‎我不确定
I'm not sure.
‎来吧
Come on.
‎为什么是这里
Why here?
‎这是什么地方
What's here?
‎我童年的房间
My childhood room.
‎别过来
Just stay back.
这对大家来说更方便
It will be quicker and easier for everyone.
‎你到底在做什么
What in hell are you doing?
‎我在打开通往无限回廊的大门
I am opening a door into the Infinite Corridor.
‎我觉得他疯了
I think his mind has gone.
‎无限回廊是个童话故事
The Infinite Corridor is a fairy tale.
‎绝对不是
It most certainly is not.
‎小姐 无限回廊
Young lady, the Infinite Corridor
通往其它世界
is a passage to other worlds.
‎但是很难控制
It is, however, very hard to control.
‎我很抱歉为了这项事业
I am truly sorry that the souls of your people
‎牺牲你们人民的灵魂
are being sacrificed to the cause,
‎但他们很快也会‎死于佝偻病
but they would have died of rickets or angry badgers
或愤怒的獾
soon enough anyway.
‎这是死亡魔法
This is death magic.
‎你用死亡的能量…
You're using the energies of death to...
‎打开回廊 直接通往地狱
To open the corridor and direct a portal to hell.
‎我想你在此杀了你父亲
And I need this spot here,
‎我需要在这个位置
where I presume you killed your father,
‎锚定连接
to anchor the connection.
‎我父亲
My father?
‎我要把他从地狱带回来
I'm bringing him back from hell.
还有你母亲
And your mother.
‎欢迎你留下来围观 ‎
You're welcome to stay and watch.
要是你愿意 你可以挥手欢迎
You can wave if you like.
‎我要杀了你
I am going to fucking murder you!
‎不 那可不行
No, I don't think so.
‎我在林登菲尔德发现
You see, in Lindenfeld I saw
‎一个多灵魂的魔法生物
that a many-souled creature of magic
‎可以控制无限回廊
can control the corridor.
‎我 圣日耳曼
I, Saint Germain,
‎将从地狱带回 ‎德古拉伯爵和丽莎·特佩斯
am going to pull Dracula and Lisa Tepes out of hell,
‎融合他们的灵魂
fuse their souls together
‎把他们注入同体者的身体
and lock them inside the body of a Rebis.
‎同体者是什么
Who's Rebis?
‎这是两性生物的说法
It's a word for a hermaphrodite creature.
‎身体里既有男人 也有女人
A body that is both man and woman.
‎炼金术的最高境界
The pinnacle of alchemy.
‎就是终极实体
An ultimate entity.
撤掉护盾 我会让你活下去
Drop this shield and I will let you live.
‎在这个过程中 我无法控制回廊
I can't control the corridor while I'm in there.
‎我还不够强大
I'm not strong enough.
‎但是一个多灵魂的生物...
But a many-souled creature...
‎甚至是吸血鬼和人类的融合
a fusion of vampire and human, even,
‎将成为控制无限回廊的关键
that would be a mechanism to exert control over the corridor.
‎已经紧密相连的吸血鬼和人类
Vampire and human who were already closely bonded.
‎显而易见
It was obvious, really.
‎为什么是现在 ‎有什么理由
Why, man? What possible reason?
‎两个理由
Two reasons.
‎我爱的女人消失在
The woman I love is lost somewhere
无限回廊里
in the Infinite Corridor.
‎而我是炼金师
And I am an alchemist.
‎我追求知识的完美
I seek the perfection of knowledge,
‎完成伟大的作品
the achievement of the great work,
旷世杰作
the magnum opus,
‎可以通过创造同体者来实现
which can be reached by the creation of the Rebis,
‎神圣的雌雄同体
the divine hermaphrodite,
融合男性和女性 ‎打造拥有完美力量和知识的
the fusion of male and female into an alchemical creature
炼金产物
of perfect power and knowledge.
‎我可以驾驭它 阿鲁卡多
And I can fucking ride it, Alucard.
‎我创造它 我结合它
I create it. I bind it.
‎我拥有它
I own it.
‎我会找到我的挚爱
I will find my love.
‎我会控制无限回廊
I will command the Infinite Corridor.
‎我会‎完全进入上百万个不同的世界
I will have complete access to a million different worlds.
像上帝一样
Like God.
‎我们不能留在这里 楼下在战斗
We can't stay here. The fight is downstairs.
‎我对赛珐·贝尔纳德斯说过
I once observed to Sypha Belnades
‎上帝早就不流行了
that God had quite gone out of fashion.
‎上帝现在就站在你面前
God is now standing right in front of you.
‎过不了多久 很快...
And soon, very, very, soon...
‎他就会再次拥有性爱
he's going to have sex again.
‎这招不错 但你把剑扔了
Good trick, but you threw away your sword.
‎我最好去把剑拿回来
I'd better go and get it.
‎保护人民
Protect the people.
‎别让他们受伤 我知道你明白怎么做
Don't wait for them to get hurt. I know you know how to do this.
‎我想你至少能奋起反抗
I thought you might at least be sporty, you know.
‎我累了
I'm tired.
而你不该戏弄你的食物
And you shouldn't play with your food.
‎你看看
Look at that.
‎就像看着你可怜的生命被一点点
It's like watching your little life being chipped away
剥皮拆骨 不是吗
down to the bone, isn't it?
‎一年多来 我在这里
More than a year I've been here,
‎假装是有用的走狗
pretending to be the useful flunky.
‎假装不是我自己
Pretending not to be who I am.
‎你知道那是什么感觉吗
Do you know what that's like?
‎隐藏我的技能 隐藏我的想法
Hiding my skills. Hiding my mind.
‎假装不是过去三百年来
Pretending not to be the best vampire war fighter
最强的吸血鬼战士 ‎以免惹恼别人
of the last 300 years, in case it upset somebody.
‎现在瓦尼可以滚远点
And now Varney can fuck off
‎剩下的日子去给德古拉当舔狗
to give Dracula hand jobs for the rest of time
‎我可以继续做我擅长的事
and I can get on with what I'm good at.
杀了你
Killing you.
‎你有没有碰到我
Did you fucking touch me?
‎你他妈的敢碰我吗
Did you dare fucking touch me?
‎你不是世界末日
You are not the apocalypse.
‎你只是个普通人
You are just a man.
‎我的人民会活得比你长
And my people will survive you.
‎我他妈是不死之身
I am fucking immortal.
‎没有人是不死之身
Nobody is immortal.
去你妈的
Fuck your eyes!
‎替我完成使命
Finish it for me.
‎镜子在哪里
Where is it?
‎我在跟你们说话 你们这些混蛋
I'm talking to you, you dusty shits.
‎好吧 ‎你们这些聪明的混蛋
Well, you clever bastards.
‎你没事吧
Are you all right?
‎可能没事 你怎么样
Probably not. You?
‎在床上躺一年 什么毛病都会好
Nothing a year in bed wouldn't cure.
‎天啊
Oh, God.
‎现在怎么办
What now?
‎伦敦的瓦尼
Varney of London.
‎你的同谋和资助人
Your conspirator and benefactor.
‎我是来亲自监督这个…
I have come to personally supervise this...
‎这个…
this...
-"这个"什么  -我...
- "This"? - Well, I was...
‎实际上 我想用个很夸张的词
Actually, I was looking for a really big word.
‎你看起来很聪明
You seem clever,
‎重要的是 你知道我也很聪明
and it's important that you know that I'm clever too.
‎先生 我相信你的智慧
Sir, I am certain your wit is as suave
‎像你独特的体味一样文雅
as your unique personal stench.
‎文雅吗 噢 文雅
Suave? Oh, suave.
这个词太短了 不是吗
Well, that's a short word, isn't it?
‎我是说 谢谢夸奖
I mean, I appreciate that.
‎"划时代的事件" ‎怎么样
How about "epochal event"?
‎随便你吧
Well, suit yourself.
‎我知道这个
I recognize that.
‎视角在移动
The point of view is moving.
‎为什么会这样
Why's that?
‎镜子锁定的地点在漂移
The mirror's location lock is drifting.
‎如果我们要进去 ‎现在就得走
If we're going to go, we're going to have to go now.
准备好了吗
Ready?
‎没有
Hell, no.
不过 准没准备好从来都阻碍不了我们
But when's that ever stopped us?